healthji.com 2015-02-11

# Health & Wellness Programs, Corporate Health Programs, Health Products, Sports Nutrition, Employee Health & Wellness Programs | Healthji

At HealthjiTM, we respect your privacy and believe you should be informed about how we collect, use and disclose your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding how we use and share with third parties Personal Information (as defined below) that we collect on the Website. By visiting the Healthji.com website and any other URLs and websites administered by EZ-Healthline, and its affiliates (collectively, the Website) submitting your Personal Information to us, you accept the practices described in this statement. The terms "you" and "user" as used herein refer to all individuals and/or entities accessing the Website for any reason.

**Terms of Use**

Your use of the Website is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and [the Terms of Use](http://www.healthji.com/terms-and-condition.php "Terms to use"), so please read this policy and the Terms of Use before using the Website.

**Age Requirement**

In order to use the Website you must be at least 18 years of age or the legal age to form a binding contract in your jurisdiction if that age is greater than 18 years of age. Please see the Terms of Use for additional information regarding this requirement.

**Personal Information**

The term Personal Information means information that identifies you as an individual, including your name, address, email address, telephone number, age, weight, and gender. We may ask you to submit Personal Information at various places on our Website, including by providing Registration Data, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting feedback. HealthjiTM also stores the information you enter about foods, activities, goals, and all other information collected in our online forms. We maintain lists of users and use the Personal Information on those lists to contact you or send you information you have requested or that we feel will be of interest to you. We may contact you via phone, email, or postal mail. We generally provide an option for you to choose not to receive these types of communications. However, even if you request not to be contacted by us, we reserve the right to use your contact information if we consider it necessary to send you information about the operation of the site, including information regarding the services you have signed up for on the Website or information about changes to our Privacy Policy. For more information about how to opt-out of receiving emails or third party offers, please click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email sent to you by HealthjiTM. Posts submitted to the Community Pages are not confidential and may be viewed by other users and the general public.

**Non-Personally Identifying Information**

Even if you do not provide us with personal information, we collect non-personal information about your use of our Site. 

We may use "Cookies" and "Web Beacons" to collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information about your use of our Site. For example, we may use cookies to help you navigate our Site more efficiently and statistically monitor how many people are using our Site. "Cookies" are small text records used by our system that allow us to track user requests and tailor the resulting user experience while on our Site. "Web Beacons" are tiny graphic image files, embedded in a web page in GIF, jpeg or HTML format, that provide a presence on the web page and send back to its home server (which can belong to the host site, a network advertiser or some other third party) information from your browser, such as the IP address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the type of browser that is accessing the Site and the ID number of any Cookies on your computer previously placed by that server. Web Beacons may also be used to place a Cookie on your computer. HealthjiTM also archives log files and uses non-personally identifying information in aggregate form to detect errors with the Website, identify security issues, and build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of HealthjiTM users, and measure demographics and interests in connection with specific areas of the Website. We may provide such statistical data to our advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business.

**Use of your Personal Information**

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to provide the services you have requested or authorized.

We may use non-personal information for research purposes, and we may provide this information in the aggregate to third parties. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of our Site and the activities they conduct while on our Site.

We contract with other companies and individuals to help us provide services. For example, we may host some of our Site on another company's computer, or we may hire a company to answer customer questions, send information about our products and other services. In order to perform their jobs, these other companies may have limited access to some of the information we maintain about you. We require all such companies to comply with the terms of our Privacy Policy, to limit their access to any personal information to the minimum necessary to perform their obligations, and not to use the information they may access for purposes other than fulfilling their responsibilities to us.

If we transfer a business unit (such as a subsidiary) or an asset (such as a web site) to another company, we will require them to honor the applicable terms of this Privacy Policy. In the event that Healthji or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, personally identifiable information will be among the transferred assets. 

We may release personal information to third parties: (1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (2) in special cases, such as in response to a physical threat to you or others, to protect property or defend or assert legal rights. In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose your personal information to a third party, we will attempt to notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order. When we share information with third parties, we ask that they agree in writing to abide by our Privacy Policy. 

Other than the cases described above, we will not release personal information about you to a third party without your consent. 

**Security of your Personal Information**

We have implemented technology and security policies, rules and other measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. We also protect your information by requiring that all our employees and others who have access to or are associated with the processing of your data respect your confidentiality. 

Although Healthji makes every reasonable attempt to secure your information, there is always some risk in transmitting information over the Internet. There is always a risk that thieves could find some way to circumvent our security systems. Although we take appropriate measures to protect your information, we cannot guarantee that the personal information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.   
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, wish to access your personal information or request that we not use your personal information for a particular purpose, please contact us at [customer_service@healthji.com](mailto:customer_service@healthji.com) . We try to answer all inquiries within a reasonable time, but may not always be able to do so.
